Swindle is a comedy, crime, tv movie film directed by Jonathan Judge.
A boy named Griffin finds a valuable multi-million dollar baseball card.
After accidentally selling the card for a million dollar loss, he enlists the help of
his best friend Ben and his colleagues to regain the baseball card.
Savannah Westcott, played by Jennette McCurdy.
Griffin Bing, played by Noah Crawford.
Darren Vader, played by Noah Munck.
Amanda Benson, played by Ariana Grande.
Melissa Bing, played by Ciara Bravo.
Ben Dupree, played by Christopher O'Neal.
Swindle is a 2013 television film starring Noah Crawford, Chris O'Neal, Jennette
McCurdy, Noah Munck, Ariana Grande, Ciara Bravo, and Fred Ewanuick.
Based on Gordon Korman's novel of the same name, the film tells the story of Griffin (Noah Crawford), a boy who retrieves
his friend's valuable baseball card from an unscrupulous collectibles dealer with the help of his friends.
Sneak peeks promoting the film aired on Nickelodeon during three Sam &
Cat episodes and the final episode of Big Time Rush.
The film premiered August 24, 2013 to an audience of over 4.2 million viewers.
The film was released on DVD on March 19, 2014,
and on Blu-ray on December 4, 2015.
The film explores themes of collector, heist, family, swindle, satirical.
The tone is lighthearted.